There are few commands which helps us to find the modules within Aosp.
We have all modes to list all the modules, so the all mod will list all the modules within the system.
Go mode will help to go to the directory containing the module path mod gets the directory containing
a module out mode, gets the location of the module installed output with certain extension.
So this will help us to find the APK files there.
Mods get the modules defined in a given directory and install mod adb install save modules build apk.
So this will help us to install the APK.
Refresh mod refresh list of modules for all mod go mod path mod out mod, etc...
So let's have a look at that.
So with all mod, it will list the entire set of modules within Aosp.
So this is a complete list of modules in Aosp and go mod will help to go to a particular module, for
example, launcher three.
So if I need to go to Launcher three directly, then go mod launcher three.
This will take me to launcher three folder and path mod.
Let's say calendar calendar.
So this will print the path of the module calendar or path mod the system UI.
So here is a path where system UI is stored and then out mod.
Let's try lambda out mod calendar so it'll give us the path from where we can pick the calendar dot
apk and we could manually install this into the device that is out mod install mod.
This will install a module so you can.
So this is similar to ADB install an APK.
So the same command.
If you say install mode calendar, this will install the calendar app into the emulator.
So it's basically executing this command ADB, install the APK and similarly install mode launcher three.
So this installed launcher three APK.
So this is pretty handy when you if you are lazy to use the ADB install command by picking up the path
and all those steps so you can simply pass the module name here of the project or package which you
are working on and then simply use install mod the module name and then we have the refresh mode.
So this will simply refresh the module information or all mod go mod path mod out mode install mod.
It's basically refreshing all those modules here.